<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>Nature Incarnate</title>
  <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/community?filter=Crowdfunding%3A%3AProjectUpdate</link>
  <description><![CDATA[Spirit Island Nature Incarnate Updates]]></description>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Monthly Update
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1909</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello, everyone. We are continuing our regularly scheduled monthly updates on the first Tuesday. For everyone in the US and elsewhere (excluding UK/EU), you should have already received your product! Please email us at <a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#hex-string"><span class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="51323e3f2530322511362334302534232539303f36303c34227f323e3c">[email&#160;protected]</span></a> if you haven’t.]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Stock in EU/UK Retail Stores
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1793</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hi, everyone. This update concerns UK/EU backers, so please disregard if you are outside of those regions.]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Insight on the UK/EU Situation
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1670</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hi again, everyone. This is another update for UK/EU backers, so please disregard if you are outside of those regions. We’ve brought in the whole Greater Than Games team for this update, as it’s important that you know we’re all working together to provide the best service possible to our community.]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Shipped out for Non-Europeans
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1706</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello again, folks. We’ve got an update for the rest of the world outside of Europe. Europeans you’re free from another update. For everyone else, if you’re not yet caught up to the European situation <a href="https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1638">here</a> and <a href="https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1670">here</a> are our most recent updates on what’s happening. ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: A Europe Update
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1638</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello, everyone. This update is for our European backers only, so our other backers, please enjoy the rest of your day.<br><br>Now, onto the update. Bailey here once again after having several meetings. I'd like to thank all of you for your patience, and a personal thank you for your kindness to me specifically. <br><br>Before answering these questions, we want to acknowledge that this is a less than ideal situation. It's pretty bad. We truly do apologize for any inconvenience created. <br><br>But, alright, what can we do about it. How are we going to move forward?<br><br>Unfortunately, the 12 week delay looks like a hard limit. There is not an alternative at this time. That 12 weeks <em>should </em>include delivery from the manufacturer to Board &amp; Dice. If there are (fate forbid it) any other shipping delays outside of that, you'll obviously be the first to know.<br><br>Here is what we can offer right now: refunds and partial refunds. Anyone who would like their pledge cancelled is more than welcome to that. You are also welcome to partial refunds! If you would like to only refund NI itself but still receive tokens or sleeves from us, partial refunds are an option.<br><br>Some of you have noticed that there are retail outlets advertising a sooner date than our 12 week estimate here. Please be advised that this was a miscommunication to the retailers. The retail release <strong>will </strong>be delayed due to this situation. This was relayed to retailers today, so there should be updates coming on estimated delivery dates.<br><br>The fastest and most effective way to receive a refund or to contact us about anything else is to email <a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="hex-string">[email&#160;protected]</a>. Comments here can unfortunately get lost due to the upvote-algorithm nature, so please please please be sure to email.<br><br>I am at the inbox right now and working through emails as quickly as possible!<br><br>Thank you for your patience with us here. And, again, we do apologize for this unfortunate situation. The good news is that the game will still deliver <em>before</em> our original projected date on this campaign, but we understand that is only a slight silver lining.<br><br>-Bailey]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: European Timeline
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1612</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hey again, folks. We do, in fact, have a timeline for European shipping! Unfortunately, it’s not great news. The EU tax law changes are providing us with a particularly challenging situation that is going to take time to work out. We essentially have to register as a business within the EU in order to ship from there and make sure our taxes (and thus yours) are above board. We’ve been told from our corporate finance department that it will be another 12 weeks.]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Tokens, Australia, and some European Delays
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1528</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Alright, folks, welcome back! We’ve got some good news and some not so good news for our European backers. I know all of you are anticipating with bated breath, so I won’t keep you too long here in the intro!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Get your addresses in now! Nature Incarnate is on the way!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1424</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Yes, that's right! It's here <em>much</em> sooner than expected! We here in St. Louis are going to be shipping out the orders for those of you who ordered just <strong><em>Nature Incarnate</em></strong> and the foils starting <strong>next Monday, June the 19th</strong>. Thus, you have until that Monday morning to get your final addresses in and updated! That means that some of you who were anticipating July deliveries may have to update your address <em>again</em>. No worries, you know what to do: reach out to <a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="hex-string">[email&#160;protected]</a> <br><br>In fact, please don't hesitate to reach out to <a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="07646869736664734760756266736275736f666960666a62742964686a">[email&#160;protected]</a> for any address (or otherwise) related reasons!<br><br>What about our foreign friends? Same as above! Board and Dice already has your <strong><em>Nature Incarnate! </em></strong>You may have different shipment timelines from our US friends, but you won't be too far off now. We're still waiting on information on other distribution centers, but we're obviously getting close to the wire! Get those surveys finished and addresses in!<br><br>We're so excited to get this shipment underway! We'll see you next update!<br><br>-Bailey]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Tokens &amp; Foils are on a Boat!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1363</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello again, everyone! Some great news to share with you all this time around: <strong><em>Premium Token Pack #2 </em></strong>and the <strong><em>Nature Incarnate Foils</em></strong> are on a boat! They are headed this way and should reach the US by the beginning of July. This means we could be shipping your copy of <strong><em>Nature Incarnate</em></strong> to you as early as late July. How exciting is that! ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Nature Incarnate is about to cross the sea!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1223</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Let’s celebrate, folks, <strong><em>Nature Incarnate</em></strong> is shipping! That’s right, the expansion is on its way! To us, that is. It has to make its way to our warehouse before we can start sending it to you. So, we aren’t completely down to the wire on changing addresses. We’ve got about a month of it crossing the ocean, then a few weeks to get to here in St. Louis. ]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Nature Incarnate in pre-ship! Foils and tokens in production!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/1098</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Good morning, everyone! Welcome back for a new update. We’ve got a short one for you this time around. We have some great news for you all: <strong><em>Nature Incarnate</em></strong> is getting ready to enter the pre-ship stage of the process! That’s right, production is wrapping up and soon will be put on the cargo containers for us. Then, it’s just a matter of time before it’s crossing the Pacific Ocean and heading right to us. Of course, there’s still the month that it takes for it to <em>cross</em> that ocean, but time will tell on exactly how long it takes. We’re on course and possibly even slightly ahead of schedule! Make sure we have your correct address!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: More pre-production and Horizons shipping out!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/929</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Welcome back again, everyone! We’ve got some good news and a little bit of clarification for you. We’re also making sure to keep <a href="https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-Incarnate/faqs#project-faqs">our project FAQ</a> up to date with questions we see the most frequently, so be sure to check there as well! Alright, without further ado, let’s get going.]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Shipping, pre-production, and more!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/836</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello again everyone! Thank you so much for following along with our updates here. There’s a short bit of news and a few topics we’d like to clarify! First, let’s get the fantastic news out of the way: the pre-production copy is in! Woo!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Horizons of Spirit Island Punch Board Panels
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/714</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Hello everyone! Welcome back to an impromptu update. This one because the item arrived a little earlier than expected! The item in question? Punch board style panels for<strong><em> Horizons of Spirit Island</em></strong>!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
              Project Update: Pre-production copy awaiting &amp; February!
            </title>
   <link>https://www.backerkit.com/c/greater-than-games/spirit-island-nature-incarnate/updates/696</link>
   <description><![CDATA[
  <div>Welcome back everyone. Now that some of you have started to get your items, we’re glad to say that we’re on schedule. First, let’s talk about what pre-production copies are all about, then we’ll get talking about the month of February, and finally we’ll be rounding off with a summary of the shipment process as it’s happening now.]]></description>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>
